vacancysoft.com 2017-09-12

# Privacy Policy - Vacancysoft

When you undertake to register yourself to receive an e-mail alert on this Website we ask for your full name, job title and e-mail address, and from time to time the e-mail addresses and additional contact details of those who communicate with us via e-mail and request information (“Personal Data”).

Any Personal Data that you give us will be treated with the utmost care and security. It will not be used in ways to which you have not consented.

The Personal Data we collect is used to provide you with the service that you have requested or to respond to an enquiry that you have made. We will not sell, rent or loan any Personal Data or identifiable information collected on this Website.

The information collected from this Website could be stored for as long as is required for the uses stated above.

If you do not want to continue to receive the alerter e-mail communications from us please let us know by sending an e-mail to [support@vacancysoft.com](mailto:support@vacancysoft.com)

A cookie is a small text file written to an individual’s hard drive that contains the user ID. The cookies do not contain any personal information about Users and in themselves only record those areas of the Website that have been visited by the computer in question, and for how long.

From time to time we may use cookies to enable us to offer certain time-saving features to our Users. These may be used to administer the Website, track Users’ movements and actions, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. The information gathered would then be used to improve the Website and the User experience.

You can find out more about the use of cookies and how you can remove them by going to the Interactive Advertising Bureau website [http://allaboutcookies.org](http://allaboutcookies.org/) or [http://www.cookiecentral.com](http://www.cookiecentral.com/). You should note that if a User sets up his browser to reject the cookie, he or she may still use the Website although functionality will be impaired.

This Website contains links to other websites, their inclusion cannot be taken to imply any endorsement or validation by us of the content of the said websites.

In order to keep up with changing legislation and best practice, we may revise this Privacy Policy at any time without notice so please check back periodically so that you are aware of any changes. This Privacy Policy should be read in conjunction with and is subject to our Terms & Conditions.

If you have any questions about this privacy pledge or feel that your privacy has been compromised, please contact us at[ support@vacancysoft.com](mailto:support@vacancysoft.com).
